Guide to the Robert S. and Eloise C. Wickham papers, 1776-1988.
Wickham, Robert S. and Eloise C. papers
- Carte-de-Visite Album, n.d. (Box 17, Volume 1)
  Carte de Visite Album, probably of Alvin R. and Alida (Mayhew) Carpenter of Schuylerville, N.Y. Many photographs were identified on the reverse, and these markings have been copied in pencil to the pages themselves, where there were already some captions. See especially four-year-old girl with rifle (p. 13), man with flute (p. 15), boy in Western Union messenger uniform (p.18). Carpenter family members: Meliza (Rich) Carpenter, Alida (Mayhew) Carpenter, Eloise Carpenter, Alvin R. Carpenter, Frank W. Rich Mayhew family members: Emily W. of Detroit, Portia of Detroit DeRidder family members: J.H. DeRidder of Springfield Friends: “son of Enoch Mudge of Boston”; Walter Edward Houghton (b. 1871) of Brooklyn; Howard Russell (b, 1876) of New Bedford; Charles Abram Russell (b, 1877); Benjamin D. Benson of New York City Faculty of Maplewood Institute, Pittsfield, Mass.: Mr. and Mrs. Spear, L.M. Johnson, Miss Gibbs, Mr. Feeder, Mr. Davenport Students of Maplewood Institute, Pittsfield, Mass.: Cora Coulter, Kitty Van Valkenburg, Hannah Durye/Burge, Mary Pettee, Oillie Allston (Chillicothe, O.), Lillie Whitman, Libbie H. Tupper (Hardwick, Mass.), Maggie Cook (Middletown, Conn.), Bell Stowe (Brooklyn), Millie Whitcomb (North Bridgewater, Mass.), Emily Nash (Troy), Sarah Edwards, Bell Morrison, Sarah Edwards (New York City), Emma W. Hubbard (Northampton, Mass.), Fanne Mather, Minnie Dayton, Georgie Masters, Mary Davis, Dotti DeFreest Students at the Naval Academy: S.D. Ames, John P. Wallis, Pat McAllister, C.M. Harris, R. Mitchell, Lieut. Bishop (instructor), E.C. Bartlett, L.S. Shook, H.C. [?Stinson], Clark Smith, Babe Doty, W.C. Strang/Strong.
- Wickham, Eloise (Carpenter)., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  School exercises, Schuylerville Union Free School, 1 of 2
- Wickham, Eloise (Carpenter)., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  School exercises, Schuylerville Union Free School, 2 of 2
- Wickham, Eloise (Carpenter)., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Papers read before the Shakespeare Club
- DeRidder, Simon, 1792, 1812 (Box 18, Volume 4)
  Regimental record book, 1812. Contains orders, muster rolls, and returns. The book had been “Sloop Pollys Account Book,” 1792, but only the records inside the front cover remain.
- 4 class caps, 1928; MU-2072 (Box 19)
- 1 class blazer, 1928; MU-2073
- Photographic Scrapbook, 1860-1956 (Box 20)
  Retained by donor Wickham, Robert S. Family photograph album, c. 1860-1956. A fine collection of family photos, many of them identified. This album was assembled using rubber cement which has entirely dried up - please use CAUTION when turning pages.